this exercise
has given us some code a method
called scream and an invocation of that
method on line
seven and we're asked to determine what
this code will print
looking at our method invocation on line
we've passed in as an argument the
string yippee
on line 2 words is reassigned
to the return value of concatenating
this string
with four exclamation marks because we
invoke put s on line four
and pass words to that invocation as an
argument
you may think that this string which
i've placed in a comment on line 7
will be printed to the screen but let's
think about the code execution in this
method
after reassigning words on line 2 when
we reach line 3 we see the reserve word
return when an explicit return like this
is executed
ruby will immediately exit from the
method
so line 4 will never be executed and we
will not output words
and we can see that when we run our code
it's important to remember that when you
explicitly return from a method
ruby exits that method immediately and
the subsequent code within that method
will not be executed